A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 71-203-22, 73-318-10, Tokyo University, Fellow, Kawata, Chieko, 1972-1973 (Box 66, Folder 1039)
  - 69-086-55, Tokyo University, Fellow, Kino, Isamu, 1969-1971, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1040)
  - CM 241-14, Tokyo University, Fellow, Kobayashi, Yoshito, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1041)
  - 65-834-22, Tokyo University, Fellow, Koizumi, Akira, 1964-1966 (Box 66, Folder 1042)
  - CM 327-12, Tokyo University, Fellow, Ogata, Tomio, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 1043)
  - 68-022-32, Tokyo University, Fellow, Takahashi, Tetsuro, 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 1044)
  - 57-397-5, Tokyo University, Fellow, Tsuge, Yoshio, 1957-1958 (Box 66, Folder 1045)
  - 66-869-31, 66-896-44, Tokyo University, Fellow, Udagawa, Eiichi, 1965-1967 (Box 66, Folder 1046)
  - CM 362-7, CM 362-15, Tokyo University, Fellow, Ueno, Shokichi, 1956-1957, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1047)
  - 57-397-4, Tokyo University, Fellow, Urata, Takeo, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 1048)
  - 64-762-51, Tokyo University, Fellow, Yoshikawa, Masaki, 1964-1966, 1969, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1049)
  - 60-533, Tokyo University, Visiting Professor, Brooks, Chandler McC., 1959-1963 (Box 67, Folder 1050)
  - 60-553, Tokyo University, Visiting Professor, Brooks, Chandler McC., Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 1051-1052)
  - 58-453, Tokyo University, Visiting Professor, Cattell, McKeen, 1958-1959 (Box 67, Folder 1053)
  - 65-814, Tokyo University,Visiting Associate Professor, Linde, Leonard M., Pediatrics, 1964-1966 (Box 67, Folder 1054)
  - CM 241-8, Tokyo Women's Medical College, Fellow, Tomita, Tsuneo, 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1055)
  - 78-375, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medicine, Endowment Fund for Medical Research and Research Planning, 1978-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990 (Box 67, Folder 1056)
  - 80-387, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medicine, Endowment Fund for Specially Selected Individuals, 1979-1995 (Box 67, Folder 1057)
  - 81-405, National Taiwan University (NTU), Medicine, Endowment for Library, 1980-1989, 1991-1995 (Box 68, Folder 1058)
  - 82-416, National Taiwan University (NTU), Postgraduate/Continuing Education, 1982, 1984-1988, 1990, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 1059)
  - 83-425, National Taiwan University (NTU), Endowment for General Development, 1983-1995 (Box 68, Frame 1060)
  - 85-435, National Taiwan University (NTU), Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1061)
  - 60-538, University of Mandalay, Books, 1960, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 1062)
  - 60-539, University of Mandalay, Equipment, 1960-1963, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 1063)
  - University of Mandalay, General, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 1064)
  - 62-645, University of Mandalay, Equipment, 1962-1964 (Box 68, Folder 1065)
  - University of Rangoon, General, 1959, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 1066)
  - CM 255, University of Rangoon, Books & Journals, 1952-1954, 1956-1958 (Box 68, Folder 1067)
  - CM 304, CM 354, University of Rangoon, Visiting Professor, Greens, Phillips F., 1953, 1955, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 1068)
  - CM 325, 60-537, University of Rangoon, 1954, 1957-1962 (Box 68, Folder 1069)
  - CM 393, University of Rangoon, Equipment, 1956-1960 (Box 68, Folder 1070)
  - CM 392, University of Rangoon, Books & Journals, 1956-1959 (Box 68, Folder 1071)
  - 58-466, University of Rangoon, 1956-1963 (Box 68, Folder 1072)
  - 61-588, University of Rangoon, Books & Journals-Library Support, 1961-1964 (Box 68, Folder 1073)
  - 61-589, University of Rangoon, Equipment, 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 1074)
  - 61-621, University of Rangoon, Equipment & SUpplies, 1960-1964 (Box 68, Folder 1075)
  - 62-644, University of Rangoon, Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1961-1964 (Box 68, Folder 1076)
  - CM 327-24, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Ba Than, U., 1956 (Box 68, Folder 1077)
  - 57-397-7, 59-474-22, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Burghall, Heather Shirley, 1957, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1078)
  - 60-541-1, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Ko Gyi, U., 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1079)
  - 57-397-29, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Law, Amy May (Ma Khin U.), 1957-1959 (Box 68, Folder 1080)
  - CM 362-18, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Lewis, Daniel R., 1957 (Box 68, Folder 1081)
  - 61-591-24, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Taik, Maung Maung, 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 1082)
  - 59-474-30, University of Rangoon, Fellow, Win, Khin Maung, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1083)
  - Trust Territory of Pacific Islands, General, 1952-1956, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 1084)
  - CM 305, CM 359, Trust Territory of Pacific Islands, Nursing Instructor, 1953-1958 (Box 69, Folder 1085)
  - CM 306, Trust Territory of Pacific Islands, Truk-Ponape Nursing School-Equipment, 1953-1954, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 1086)
  - CM 327-2, Trust Territory of Pacific Islands, Truk-Ponape School of Nursing, Fellow, Odaol, Justino, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 1087)
  - CM 323, Trust Territory of Pacific Islands, Nursing Textbooks, 1954-1956 (Box 69, Folder 1088)
  - CM 291, University of Ceylon, Books & Journals, 1953, 1956-1958, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1089)
  - University of Ceylon, General, 1956, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1090)
  - CM 241-18, University of Ceylon, Fellow, Samarasinghe, Lincoln Earle, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 1091)
  - Fiji School of Medicine, General, 1955-1956, 1961-1962, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1092)
  - CM 362-9, Fiji School of Medicine, Fellow, Tulsi, Ram Singh, 1956, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 1093)
  - 57-397-21, 58-429-18, 59-474-29, Fiji School of Medicine, Fellow, Vithal, Manek Lal, 1958-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1094)
  - 61-591-22, Fiji School of Medicine, Vudiniabola, Etika S., 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 1095)
  - University of Saigon, General, 1957-1967, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 1096)
  - 58-448, University of Saigon, Equipment, 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1097)
  - CM 350, 58-460, University of Saigon, Books & Journals, 1955-1958, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 1098)
  - 61-586, University of Saigon, Books & Journals-Equipment, 1961-1962, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1099)
  - 61-587, University of Saigon, Equipment, 1961-1964 (Box 69, Folder 1100)
  - 63-685, University of Saigon, Equipment, 1963-1964, 1966-1968 (Box 69, Folder 1101)
  - 65-846, University of Saigon, Library Support, 1965, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1102)
  - 68-053, University of Saigon, Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 69, Folder 1103)
  - 69-116, University of Saigon, Library Support, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 1104)
  - Kaohiung Medical Center, General, 1960, 1963, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1105)
  - National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), General Correspondence, Director and Staff, 1952-1956, 1960, 1965, 1969-1973, 1975-1976, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 1106)
  - National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing-General Correspondence & Background Material, 1970-1974 (Box 69, Folder 1107)
  - 73-329-8, 73-329-9, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Nursing-Fellowship Allocation, 1974, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1108)
  - 73-329-8, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1979 (Box 69, Folder 1109)
  - 73-318-2, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Fellowship Allocation, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 1110)
  - CM 252, CM 289, CM 322, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Books & Journals, 1952-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1111)
  - CM 262, CM 294, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1952-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1112)
  - CM 263, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Building, 1952, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 1113)
  - CM 293, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Surgical Laboratory, 1953-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1114)
  - CM 345, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Teaching Supplies, 1955-1958 (Box 69, Folder 1115)
  - CM 386, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Books & Journals, 1956-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1116)
  - CM 387, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Cariology-Pulmonary & Other Laboratories, 1956-1958 (Box 69, Folder 1117)
  - CM 388, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Surgical Laboratory, 1956-1959 (Box 70, Folder 1118)
  - 60-525, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-Clinical & Pre-clinical, 1959-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1119)
  - 60-556, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-Clinical & Pre-Clinical, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1120)
  - 60-557, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Biochemistry & Physiology, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1121)
  - 60-558, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Building Construction-Classrooms, 1960-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1122)
    2014:022, SG 1:053, 2014:022, SG 1:054
  - 60-588, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Building Construction-Classrooms, 1960-1962; 2014:022, SG 1:053
  - 60-558, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Building Construction-Classrooms, 1960-1962; 2014:022, SG 1:054
  - 60-559, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Radiation Therapy Training Center, 1960-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1123)
  - 60-560, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment & Supplies, 1960, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1124)
  - 61-609, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-Clinical & Pre-clinical, 1961-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1125)
  - 61-573, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Books & Journals-Library Support, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1126)
  - 62-654, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-Clinical &Pre-clinical, 1962-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1127)
  - 62-665, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Books & Jounrals, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 1128)
  - 63-723, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Supplies & Equipment, 1963-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1129)
  - 62-666, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Classroom & Laboratory Improvement-General Correspondence & Original Lists, 1959, 1962-1964 (Box 70, Folder 1130)
    2014:022, SG 1:055
  - 62-666, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Classroom & Laboratory Improvement-General Correspondence & Original Lists, 1959, 1962-1964; 2014:022, SG 1:055
  - 62-667, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment & Supplies, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1131)
  - 63-681, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment & Supplies, 1963-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1132)
  - 63-724, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research Equipment, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 1133)
  - 63-726, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Radiation Therapy Training, 1963, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1134)
  - 57-403, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, 1957-1959 (Box 70, Folder 1135)
  - 57-404, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Extension, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 1136)
    2014:022, SG 1:056
  - 57-404, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Extension, 1957; 2014:022, SG 1:056
  - 58-444, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-Department of Pharmacy, 1958-1959 (Box 70, Folder 1137)
  - 58-454, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Animal House, 1958-1959 (Box 70, Folder 1138)
    2014:022, SG 1:057
  - 58-454, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Animal House, 1958-1959; 2014:022, SG1:057
  - 58-455, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1959-1961 (Box 70, Folder 1139)
  - 59-484, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, 1959-1961 (Box 70, Folder 1140)
  - 59-494, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Books & Journals, 1958-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1141)
  - 59-508, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Rehabilitation-Surgery Department, 1959, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 1142)
    2014:022, SG 1:058 2044:022, SG 1:059
  - 59-508, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Rehabilitation-Surgery Department, 1959, 1961; 2014:022, SG 1:058
    Oversized architectural drawing-Sketch of Remodel Surgical Lab & Sugical Audio-Visual Classroom
  - 59-508, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Rehabilitation-Surgery Department, 1959, 1961; 2014:022, SG 1:059
    Oversized architectual drawing-Construction of Laboratory for Surgery Department
  - 59-509, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Clinical Laboratories, 1959-1961 (Box 70, Folder 1143)
  - 64-747, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Central Medical Research Laboratories, 1963-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 1144)
  - 64-748, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Teaching Health Center, 1964-1967 (Box 70, Folder 1145)
  - 64-771, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Pathology, Microscopes, 1964-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1146)
  - 64-781, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Cardiology & Cardiac Surgery, 1964-1966 (Box 70, Folder 1147)
  - 64-782, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Research, 1964-1968, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1148)
  - 65-815, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, Clinical & Pre-clinical, Research, 1965-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1149)
  - 65-816, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Support, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1150)
  - 65-817, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Interdepartmental Research Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 71, Folder 1151)
  - 65-843, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research Equipment-Clinical & Pre-clinical, 1965-1966 (Box 71, Folder 1152)
  - 65-855, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Clinical Research, 1965, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 1153)
  - 66-881, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Clinical Research, 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1154)
  - 66-912, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Support, 1966-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1155)
  - 66-913, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1966-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1156)
  - 67-947, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, 1967-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1157)
  - 67-972, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1967-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1158)
  - 68-0110, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Requests, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 1159)
  - 68-039, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, 1968-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1160)
  - 68-040, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1161)
  - 69-068, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1162)
  - 69-058, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1163)
  - 67-973, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1967-1969 (Box 71, Frame 11964)
  - 66-914, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1165)
  - 66-882, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 1166)
  - 65-854, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 1167)
  - 68-038, 69-090, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Kohlberg laboratory, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 1168)
  - 69-069, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Electron Microscope, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 1169)
  - 69-100, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1971 (Box 72, Folder 1170)
  - 69-101, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1970, 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1171)
  - 69-102, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1172)
  - 70-126, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Bio-Medical Laboratory, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1173)
  - 70-127, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1174)
  - 70-156, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1175)
  - 70-157, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1176)
  - 71-183, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment-Otorhinolaryngology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1177)
  - 71-184, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1178)
  - 71-214, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1179)
  - 71-215, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1180)
  - 72-248 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1181)
  - 72-276 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1182)
  - 73-312 I, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1183)
  - 58-429-22, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chai, Charles Chok-yung, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 1184)
  - 71-203-23, 73-318-2 National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chang, Gu-gang, 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1185)
  - 62-647-30, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chang, Nsin-shiang, 1962-1964, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1186)
  - CM 327-10, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chang, Hsien-lin, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 1187)
  - 65-834-13, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Change, Te Lin, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 1188)
  - CM 362-3, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chang, Yu-han, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 1189)
  - 70-141-10, 71-203-18, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chao, Hsia fu, 1970-1973 (Box 72, Folder 1190)
  - 60-541-41, 60-591-62, 62-647-56, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chao, Ping-yu, 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 1191)
  - 67-938-69, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chao, Shio-hsiung, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 1192)
  - 73-318-2, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Gran-Hum, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 1193)
  - 59-474-32, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Joseph Shanchiu, 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 1193)
  - 65-834-52, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Kuang-Yao, 1966-1971 (Box 72, Folder 1194)
  - 65-834-48, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Liang-Foo, 1965-1967 (Box 72, Folder 1195)
  - 68-022-26, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chen, Li-chuen, 1968-1969 (Box 72, Folder 1196)
  - 65-834-53, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Cheng, Bu-fei, 1965-1967 (Box 73, Folder 1197)
  - 59-474-33, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ch'i, I-cheng, 1960-1961, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1198)
  - 62-647-17, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chiang, Hsu-tung, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 1199)
  - 58-429-8, 59-494-45, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chiang, Tze-chun, 1958, 1960, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 1200)
  - 66-896-56, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chien, Kwang-yu, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 1201)
  - 68-022-38, 69-086-47, 70-141-25, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Ching, King-Nien, 1967-1971 (Box 73, Folder 1202)
  - 63-694, 64-762-49, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chou, Bon-you, 1963-1964 (Box 73, Folder 1203)
  - 60-541-42, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chou, Tao-hsiang, 1961-1962, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 1204)
  - 67-936-7, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chou, Wei-chung, 195, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1205)
  - 68-022-15, 69-086-6, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chow, Sien-yao, 1968-19710 (Box 73, Folder 1206)
  - CM 259-15, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chu, Bon-you, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 1207)
  - 65-834-10, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chu, Fuli, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 1208)
  - 59-474-34, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Chu, Shi-ping, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 1209)
  - 57-397-34, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Fan, Ping-chin, 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 73, Folder 1210)
  - CM 279-11, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Feng, Teh-tseng, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1211)
  - 63-694-33, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Feng, Teh-tseng, 1963-1965, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 1212)
  - 58-429-23, 59-474-44, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Feng, Wen-kiang, 1959-1961, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 1213)
  - 58-429-10, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hou, Hio-hi, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 1214)
  - 65-834-40, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hsieh, Yuan-Ching, 1965, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 1215)
  - 59-474-11, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hsu, Chih-yun, 1959-1961 (Box 73, Folder 1216)
  - 66-896-57, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hsu, Wan-yin, 1966-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1217)
  - CM 362-24, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hung, Tsu-sen, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 1218)
  - 59-474-35, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hsueh, James Yu-hsing, 1960-1961 (Box 73, Folder 1219)
  - 67-938-63, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hu, Jun-teh, 1967-1970 (Box 73, Folder 1220)
  - 68-0333-43, 69-086-58, 70-141-51, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Huang, Siu-Wen, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 1221)
  - 61-591-44, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hwang, Yun-Fei, 1962, 1964-1965, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 1222)
  - CM 259-16, CM 279-7, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Hwei, Chien-Yuen, 1953-1954 (Box 73, Folder 1223)
  - 59-474-36, 61-591-5, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Jen, Tien-ming, 1960-1961 (Box 73, Folder 1224)
  - CM 241-5, National Defense Medical Center (NDMC), Medical School, Fellow, Jung, Pao Feng, 1952, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 1225)